okay it's a quarter till get started
好吧，这是开始之前的四分之一
with these shorter sessions gonna have
这些较短的会议将有
to keep moving quickly so going to be
保持快速移动，因此
talking today about lambdas and ways
今天谈论lambda和方式
that you can use them to simplify your
您可以使用它们来简化您的
code quick agenda so you can decide if
代码快速议程，以便您可以决定是否
you want to leave right away we'll start
你想马上离开我们就开始
off with a very quick review of lambdas
快速评估lambdas
I'm assuming that most everyone here I'm
我假设这里的大多数人
hoping everyone here has seen lambdas
希望这里的每个人都看到过lambdas
worked with them a little bit in Java
在Java中与他们一起工作了一点
eight but we'll do a really quick review
八，但我们会做一个非常快速的回顾
first and then we'll show some neat
首先，然后我们将展示一些简洁
tricks you can do with them take a
您可以使用它们的技巧
little bit of time out to talk about how
有点时间谈论如何
to deal with checked exceptions and then
处理检查的异常，然后
talk about some ways that you can take
谈论一些你可以采取的方法
design patterns and turn them into
设计模式并将其转化为
library methods and then finally show a
库方法，然后最后显示一个
few ways that you can maybe increase the
几种可能可以增加
static type checking of your code add
您的代码的静态类型检查添加
some type safety using lambdas now I
现在使用lambda进行某种类型的安全性I
want to stress that the idea here is not
想强调一点，这里的想法不是
that you walk away with the specific
你与特定的走开
techniques I've shown I'm showing
我所展示的技术我所展示的
although you're certainly welcome to do
虽然当然欢迎您这样做
that what I really want you to do is to
我真正想要你做的是
get inspired and think about other ways
受到启发并考虑其他方式
that as you are doing your daily jobs or
在您做日常工作时
your you know nightly hacking you run
你知道你每天晚上黑客运行
into things and think hey lambdas can
进入事物，并认为嘿lambdas可以
make this better so a quick word about
让它变得更好，以便快速地说一下
me I work at myriad genetics where we do
我在无数的遗传学工作
testing of genes to determine a person's
测试基因以确定一个人的
predisposition to getting cancer been
易患癌症
working in java for about 17 years
在Java中工作约17年
occasionally I'll tweet occasionally
我偶尔会发推文
I'll commit code and occasionally I'll
我提交代码，偶尔我会
speak here at JavaOne okay last thing
在JavaOne上讲一下最后一件事
before we get rolling I want to make it
在我们开始滚动之前，我要做到
clear that not necessarily everything
清楚不一定是所有
I'm showing you is the most performant
我向您展示的是表现最好的
way to do something if you're writing a
如果您正在写一个做某事的方法
real-time life-saving application these
实时救生应用这些
this might not be the right strategy to
这可能不是正确的策略
use although it may be however in most
尽管在大多数情况下可能会使用
situations for example if you're in an
情况，例如，如果您处于
application that also has to talk to a
也必须与
database or do any other sort of i/o
数据库或其他任何类型的I / O
wait the extra penalty that might be
等待可能会产生的额外罚款
incurred by using lambdas in these ways
通过这些方式使用lambda引起的
is
是
going to be miniscule but you know if
会很小，但是你知道
you're concerned do some benchmarks
您担心要进行一些基准测试
check it out okay so first of all what
检查出来好吧，首先
are lambdas well they obviously they
是lambdas，他们显然是
were introduced in Java eight they
是在Java 8中引入的
they're more than just anonymous inner
他们不只是匿名内心
classes with some syntactic sugar
一些语法糖的课程
although if it helps you to think about
虽然如果它可以帮助您考虑
them that way go ahead because it'll
他们那样前进，因为它将
give you a reasonably accurate model of
给你一个合理准确的模型
how things end up working out the key is
事情最终如何解决的关键是
that they're represented a lambda
他们代表一个lambda
expression is represented by a interface
表达式由接口表示
that has exactly one non default method
只有一种非默认方法
you can add default methods to the
您可以将默认方法添加到
interface all day long
全天候界面
but it has to have exactly one method to
但是它必须有一种方法
be introduced otherwise a single lambdas
否则将引入单个lambda
not going to do the trick wouldn't know
不去做把戏就不会知道
which interface method you're talking
您在说哪种接口方法
about so in in in full generality they
大概如此，他们
look like this they say hey I've got a
他们说，嘿，我有一个
function from string to integer I take
从字符串到整数的函数
in a string s and then what do i do I've
在字符串s中，然后我该怎么办
got this block of code to get the length
得到了这段代码以获取长度
but we can of course you know get rid of
但是我们当然可以知道摆脱
the the string repetition there and we
那里的字符串重复，我们
can for that matter get rid of the curly
为此可以摆脱卷曲
braces and the return and and we're
大括号和返回和我们
already feeling a little better and then
已经感觉好一点了，然后
we realize that S has no purpose being
我们意识到S没有目的
there so we can just say this so if this
在那里，我们可以这样说，如果这
is new to you I apologize the rest of
对您来说是新手，对不起
the talk might be a little bit difficult
谈话可能会有点困难
to follow okay
跟着走
most likely when you first saw lambdas
最有可能在您第一次看到Lambda时
introduced you saw them introduced in
介绍您看到他们介绍
the in the form of streams and you you
以流的形式，你
probably saw some example like this you
大概看到这样的例子你
saw yeah let's say I've got a bunch of
看到是的，我说我有一堆
employees and I want to find the
员工，我想找到
salaries of just the engineers and I
只是我和工程师的薪水
want to do it
想做
average by city and so you you write
平均城市，所以你写
something like this first I can filter
这样的东西我可以过滤
out my engineers so I'm just looking at
我的工程师，所以我只是看着
my employees so I'm just looking at
我的员工，所以我只是看
engineers and then I can group by the
工程师，然后我可以按
employees city and then finally I can
员工城市，最后我可以
average their salaries up and this is
平均他们的工资，这是
really nice I mean we're looking at five
真的很好，我是说我们要看五个
lines of code here that in earlier
前面的代码行
versions of Java would have taken easily
Java版本会很容易
two to three times as many lines
线的两到三倍
code now the only on the bright side
现在编码唯一的好处
though you would have had to write more
虽然你本来不得不写更多
code it would have also been harder to
代码，它也将更难
read and so your job security would have
阅读，这样您的工作安全就可以了
been increased but at least at least now
增加，但至少至少现在
if we're comfortable with our job
如果我们对工作感到满意
security we can we can be a little bit
安全我们可以一点点
more expressive it's also easier to see
更具表现力，也更容易看到
whether or not there's bugs and of
是否存在错误和
course the the original motivation for
当然，最初的动机是
adding all of this was to support
添加所有这些都是为了支持
parallel processing because there's
并行处理，因为
nothing in here that can't be done in
在这里什么都做不了
parallel should you choose all right so
你应该选择平行吗
streams are nice but that's really not
流很好，但是那真的不是
what we're gonna be talking about today
今天我们要谈论的是
instead I want to talk about some other
相反，我想谈谈其他
ways so first thing null safe navigation
第一件事使安全导航无效
how many of you have ever programmed in
你们有多少人编程过
groovy a few so you might recognize what
杂乱无章，所以您可能会意识到
this is up here it's it sort of looks
这是这里看起来
like Java code I'm invoking a get
像Java代码一样，我正在调用get
address method but there's that little
地址方法，但有那么一点
question mark in front of the dot and
点前面的问号和
and then with each subsequent method
然后使用每个后续方法
chain call there's that question mark
连锁电话有那个问号
and all that means is please invoke the
这意味着请调用
method that I'm saying to invoke on the
我要在上调用的方法
object that I just mentioned unless that
我刚才提到的对象，除非那样
object happens to be null in which case
在这种情况下，对象恰好为null
never mind just giving me no back and so
没关系，只要不给我任何回报，等等
the idea is if you're in a space where
这个想法是，如果你在一个空间里
where anything might be null and you
那里什么都可能为空，而你
need to be careful then you can use this
需要小心，然后才能使用此
mode of you know getting data and and
您知道获取数据的方式，并且
and not worry about getting a null
不用担心会得到null
pointer exception now of course if you
当然，如果您现在指针异常
if you haven't or have programmed groovy
如果您还没有编程过
but you also like Java you think you
但您也喜欢Java，以为您
know it's actually not that big of an
知道实际上并没有那么大
advantage because in Java it's pretty
优势，因为在Java中它很漂亮
easy I just have to check is the
简单，我只需要检查的是
employee null or not and if if the
员工是否为null，如果
employee isn't no oh I should check the
员工不是吗，我应该检查一下
address as well and and then I should
以及，然后我应该
probably check the city of the address
可能检查地址的城市
of the employee and and and ok once I've
员工，然后一旦我确定
figured all that out I can actually
我想通了所有这些
safely invoke it and so you know after
安全地调用它，所以你知道之后
you after you write this sort of thing
你写完这类东西之后
you get sad and and and you're sad
你会难过，然后你会难过
because I mean you're looking at this
因为我是说你在看这个
you're there's a lot of repetition
你有很多重复
there's of course you know I mean the
你当然知道我的意思是
more methods you chain it's actually o
您链接的更多方法实际上是
of N squared code that you
的N个平方代码
- right unless you do some other tricks
-是的，除非您做了其他技巧
with temporary variables either way it's
与临时变量无论哪种方式
not happy so in Java 8 the first thought
不开心，所以在Java 8中第一个想法
you might have is let's refactor the
您可能拥有的是让我们重构
domain entirely to use optional anyplace
域完全可以使用任意位置
there could be a null and if you can do
可能为空，如果可以的话
that that's great and that's probably
那太好了，那可能是
the best route but if you can't do that
最好的路线，但是如果你做不到
if you are gonna have to deal with the
如果您要处理
domain where there can be nulls we can
我们可以有空值的域
still use optional or at least maybe
仍然使用可选或至少可能
abuse it I haven't quite decided whether
虐待它，我还没有决定
this constitutes an abuse or not but it
这是否构成滥用，但是
sure is convenient and basically what we
当然很方便，基本上我们
do is we use optionals of nullable
我们是否使用nullable的可选
method at the start so that that'll
一开始的方法，这样
either give me a present optional with
要么给我一个礼物可选
an employee or an empty optional if
雇员或空的可选
employee was null and then we start
员工为空，然后我们开始
indicating which methods to invoke this
指示哪些方法可以调用此方法
is optionals map method which will
是可选的map方法，它将
invoke the method if it's a present
如果存在，则调用该方法
optional and obviously not if it's an
可选的，如果不是
empty optional and then when we're done
空可选，然后当我们完成时
we'll say or else know if that's what
我们会说或者不知道那是什么
you want you might want to say or else
你想你可能想说其他
throw if it's a if it's a big problem
如果是大问题就扔
but the idea here is that now we have
但是这里的想法是，现在我们有了
type safe navigation and and the reason
键入安全导航以及原因
this works is because we're no longer
这行得通是因为我们不再
saying okay here's what I want to do
说好，这就是我想要做的
right now I need to call this method
现在我需要调用此方法
than this method instead we're saying
而不是这种方法
here are some things I'd like to do but
这是我想做的一些事情，但是
I'm not going to do them I'm gonna ask
我不会去问他们
the optional class to do them for me and
为我和他们做的可选班
it can smartly decide whether or not to
它可以明智地决定是否
do them and that's kind of be a
做他们，那有点像
recurring theme throughout throughout
贯穿整个主题
this but in any case you know this makes
这个，但是无论如何你都知道
us happy so so that that's good another
我们很高兴，所以这是另一个好
example and I apologize for moving
的例子，我为搬家表示歉意
quickly here with the new 45 minute
新的45分钟很快在这里
length trying to get through everything
试图通过一切的长度
if possible another thing sometimes you
如果可能的话，有时候你
have a list of objects and you want to
有一个对象列表，你想
sort of take the first one that's not
拿第一个不是的
null you know the the first ones better
null，您知道第一个更好
than the second the second better than
比第二要好
the third but nulls not better than not
第三，但空值总比没有好
null so you know there's various
null，所以您知道有各种各样
libraries that can do this commons Lang
可以做到这一点的图书馆Lang
is one of them it has an object utils
是其中之一，它具有对象utils
class which has a first non null method
具有第一个非null方法的类
and it kind of does exactly what you
它确实可以满足您的需求
think it would do it takes in a bunch of
认为这样做会花费很多
references and says the first one that's
引用并说第一个是
not null that's the one I'm going to
不是null那是我要去的那个
give you back
还给你
and if they're all no I'll give you no
如果他们都不是，我不会给你
back so this is fine as long as all the
返回，所以只要所有
data that you're providing or at least
您提供的数据或至少
all the data after the first instance
第一个实例之后的所有数据
are cheap to provide that it's cheap to
便宜，只要它便宜
compute ahead of time but that's not
提前计算，但这不是
always the case for example if you're
总是这样，例如，如果您
running an e-commerce site and you say
运行一个电子商务网站，您说
all right well I want to get some
好吧，我想得到一些
recommendations to the customer to
给客户的建议
convince them to buy even more things
说服他们买更多的东西
they don't need and so the first thing
他们不需要，所以第一件事
I'll do is I'll look at what's in their
我要做的就是看看他们的内在
shopping cart and see if I can get some
购物车，看看我能不能得到一些
recommendations based off of that and if
基于此的建议，如果
that doesn't work then let me see if I
那不起作用，然后让我看看我是否
can get recommendations based off the
可以根据
customer history and if that doesn't
客户历史记录，如果没有
work now let me just give up and show
现在工作，让我放弃并展示
them some of our bestsellers so that's
他们一些我们的畅销书，所以
all nice and good but the problem is
一切都很好，但问题是
that each of these activities might be
这些活动可能是
fairly expensive to do and and moreover
做起来相当昂贵，而且
I mean if we're trying to sort of
我的意思是，如果我们试图
minimize the amount of work we do then
减少我们要做的工作量
if it turns out the cart was able to
如果事实证明购物车能够
give us recommendations then we wasted
给我们建议，然后我们浪费了
time computing the other things
时间计算其他事情
conversely if it turns out that the cart
相反，如果事实证明购物车
recommendation process takes a long time
推荐过程需要很长时间
to come back and say no well then you
回来说不好那么你
know all that time if I wanted to give
知道所有的时间，如果我想给
my customer a very good experience I
我的客户一个很好的经历
would have been already calculating
本来已经在计算
other possible sources of
其他可能的来源
recommendations so with and again the
建议如此反复
problem here is that we did all this
这里的问题是我们做了所有这一切
work before we call it optional and so
在我们将其称为可选之前工作
when when you do that in Java a bunch of
当您在Java中执行此操作时
arguments it's going to calculate the
参数将要计算
arguments values in a defined sequence
定义序列中的参数值
so this this you know it makes us sad
所以你知道这让我们伤心
but what we can do instead is we can say
但是我们可以做的就是说
all right I want to have first not null
好吧，我想先不为空
be a method that takes in lambdas in
是将lambda引入
this case these these would be suppliers
在这种情况下，这些将是供应商
and so now we simply say here's the work
所以现在我们只说这是工作
that I want done and I want to get the
我想完成，我想得到
first non null thing and this starts to
第一个非null的东西，这开始
make a lot more sense because we've got
更有意义，因为我们有
suppliers we can either say don't do the
我们可以说不做的供应商
work if I don't need to or we can say I
工作，如果我不需要，或者我们可以说我
want to paralyze it do it all at the
想让它瘫痪
same time to maximize responsiveness and
同时最大化响应速度和
the method to do this is is really
方法是真的
straightforward I mean I'm sure there's
直率的我是说我确定
a library that has it but it's hardly
有它的图书馆，但几乎没有
worth looking for a library for this
值得为此寻找图书馆
amount of code basically you take the
基本上，您需要使用大量的代码
stream of the values that are passed in
传入的值流
which are really suppliers and then the
真正是供应商，然后
first thing you do is you say I want the
你要做的第一件事就是你说我想要
I want to invoke the get method and then
我想调用get方法，然后
I want to filter out the ones that
我想过滤掉那些
aren't know and then finally take the
不知道，然后最终采取
first element and if if nothing's
第一个元素，如果没有的话
present then I'll just I'll just return
现在，我就回去
null and of course because of the way
null，当然是因为
the streams work if I do this in serial
如果我串行执行此流
it's actually not going to do any extra
它实际上不会做任何额外的操作
work beyond what it has to and if I do
工作超出了我必须要做的
it in parallel then everything you know
它并行，那么你知道的一切
if fork/join works out the way we want
如果fork / join符合我们想要的方式
it and so forth everything can can get
等等一切都可以得到
done quickly ok so you know once again
很快就做好了，所以你再次知道
we're happy ok one problem that you can
我们很高兴你可以解决一个问题
run into sometimes though one of the
有时会遇到
great things I should say about Java is
关于Java我应该说的很棒的事情是
that with with the introduction of
随着介绍
lambdas any interface that had just a
lambdas仅有一个接口的任何接口
single method automatically became
单一方法自动成为
eligible to to be lambda eyes or
有资格成为lambda眼睛或
whatever that word would be but some
不管那个词是什么，但有些
methods of course have more than or some
方法当然有更多或一些
interfaces excuse me have more than one
接口对不起，我有多个
method that they specify and so if I've
他们指定的方法，所以如果我已经
got a something like this you know
有这样的事情，你知道
there's not really anything I can do I
我真的无能为力
can't I can't do a lambda expression to
我不能做一个lambda表达式来
create an instance of this interface but
创建此接口的实例，但是
what you can do is create helper methods
您可以做的是创建辅助方法
and these helper methods can take in one
这些辅助方法可以合而为一
or more lambdas and construct an
或更多的lambda，并构造一个
instance of the interface for you so
接口实例为您服务
that you don't have to go back to the
您不必回到
old days of anonymous inner classes so a
匿名内部类的过去，所以
way that such a method might look
这种方法看起来的方式
one-one sort of full bore examples we
我们一对一的例子
say all right well the the visitor
说好游客
interface requires the file visitor
界面需要文件访问者
interface requires four methods there's
界面需要四种方法
the do I want to recurse into the
我想递归到
directory the pre visit directory then
目录，然后访问目录
there's okay here's a file I want to
好的，这是我想要的文件
look at it and then what do I do if I
看着它，然后我该怎么办
tried to look at the file and it failed
试图查看文件，但失败了
and what do I do if I try to look at the
以及如果我尝试看看
directory and it failed and these are
目录，它失败了，这些是
all functions because at each stage you
所有功能，因为在每个阶段
have
有
returned constant indicating whether you
返回常量，指示您是否
want to keep looking at more stuff or
想继续寻找更多的东西或
not so if I create a method like this
如果创建这样的方法则不是
that you know once you've written the
一旦写完就知道
signature the the of the method the
签名方法的
implementation kind of writes itself
实现自己写
where we know we're gonna need to create
我们知道我们需要创建的地方
some new say anonymous inner class and
一些新的匿名内部类，
then for the first method you know
然后你知道的第一种方法
pre-visit directory what do I do well
预先访问目录我该怎么办
gosh I was just given a path and some
天哪，我只是给了一条路和一些
file attributes and I have a lambda
文件属性，我有一个lambda
expression which will accept both of
表达将接受两个
those and it will return whatever I need
这些，它将返回我需要的一切
to return so just invoke it and the
返回，所以只需调用它和
other four other three methods you do in
您要进行的其他四种其他三种方法
exactly the same way except you don't
完全一样的方式，只是不
put them on the slide because they don't
将它们放到幻灯片上，因为它们不
fit so that's nice but it's a lot of
合适，所以很好，但是很多
work maybe in your typical use case you
在典型的用例中工作
want to just recursively go through an
只是想递归地经历一个
entire file tree you want to look at
您要查看的整个文件树
everything and you always want to keep
一切，你一直想保持
going and in that case the visit file
去，在这种情况下访问文件
method is the only interesting one so
方法是唯一有趣的方法
instead we could do something like this
相反，我们可以做这样的事情
where we just take in a single lambda
我们只接受一个lambda
expression for the thing we care about
表达我们关心的事情
and then the others can have default
然后其他人可以具有默认值
behavior it turns out there's a simple
行为证明有一个简单的
file visitor class that makes it easy to
文件访问者类，可以轻松实现
have default behavior for the methods
具有方法的默认行为
that you don't want to override do
你不想重写的
something like this so this this is a
像这样的东西，这是一个
nice improvement because you're back in
很好的改进，因为您又回来了
being able to sort of you know express
能够让你知道表达
yourself functionally there is one
自己在功能上有一个
problem hidden in it though and the
隐藏在其中的问题和
problem is that there's a good chance
问题是有很大的机会
when someone is given a file or a path
当有人得到文件或路径时
and I apologize that this is a the
我很抱歉这是一个
generic really almost is always path
泛型真的几乎总是路径
when you're when you're given one of
当您获得以下之一时
those there's a good chance that you're
那些很有可能是你
going to want to do something that might
想要做一些可能
involve IO and that means there an IO
涉及IO，这意味着那里有IO
exception can be thrown but what we did
可以抛出异常，但是我们做了什么
before was we were using the standard
在我们使用标准之前
Java interfaces in Java util function by
Java util函数中的Java接口
function and all of the interfaces in
功能和其中的所有接口
Java util the Java util function package
Java util Java util功能包
none of them declare that they throw
他们都没有宣布他们扔
exceptions and so we're gonna run into
例外，所以我们会遇到
trouble and this is this kind of goes to
麻烦，这就是这种去
a problem that was called accept
被称为接受的问题
and transparency exception transparency
和透明度例外透明度
was supposed to work is that you could
本来可以工作的是
do something like this I want to do
做这样的事情我想做
something for each file file create a
为每个文件创建一个文件
new file can throw an i/o exception but
新文件可以引发I / O异常，但
that's okay because I say that I can
没关系，因为我说我可以
throw an i/o exception upon upon the
抛出一个I / O异常
method here so that that's fine that's
方法，这样很好
great but unfortunately it if you try to
很好，但不幸的是，如果您尝试
compile it you'll if you write it in
编译它，如果您将其写入
your IDE you'll go to the red squiggly
您的IDE，您会弯腰弯腰
and it could try to compile it you're
它可以尝试编译它
going to get an error because we're
会因为我们在
saying we'd like to throw an i/o
说我们想抛出一个I / O
exception but it's incompatible with the
例外，但与
lambda the the lambda interface that
lambda的lambda接口
we're trying to the functional interface
我们正在尝试功能界面
that we're trying to convert it to and
我们正在尝试将其转换为
well gosh that's a real bummer and it
天哪，这真是一个无赖
really is a bummer if you've worked with
如果您与
lambdas much you've probably run into
lambdas，您可能会遇到
this problem you're trying to do stream
您正在尝试播放此问题
processing and suddenly you you you run
处理，突然间，您运行了
into this problem and so well the first
进入这个问题，第一个很好
thing that you could do is you could oh
你可以做的是你可以的哦
I should mention they did try to fix
我应该提到他们确实尝试修复
this but tight theories hard and it's
这个但严格的理论很难
especially hard with exceptions because
特别难，因为
they're neither covariant nor
他们既不是协变也不是
contravariant and they're a union type
相反，它们是联合类型
really because you could throw perhaps
真的是因为你可能会抛出
either an i/o exception or an
I / O异常或
interrupted exception and it's
中断的异常，它是
fascinating to read through the list of
引人入胜的阅读清单
the mailing lists to see how they they
邮件列表，看看他们如何
tried to solve this and in the end it
试图解决这个问题并最终解决
just really was not going to happen so
只是真的不会发生，所以
what are we gonna do well one thing that
我们该怎么做才能做好一件事
we can do is is we can just say well
我们能做的就是说得好
we'll catch the exception in our lambda
我们将在lambda中捕获异常
expression and if we get it we'll
表达，如果我们得到它，我们将
convert it to a runtime exception
将其转换为运行时异常
standard trick that you know you see
您知道的标准技巧
pepper it all throughout java whenever
随时在整个Java中加入胡椒
you have checked exceptions i don't know
您检查了我不知道的异常
about you but i don't feel so good about
关于你，但我感觉不太好
this
这个
this took my one-liner and blew it up
这花了我的一线，炸毁了
into a I don't know seven eight liner
变成了我不知道的七八班轮
it's got a whole bunch of stuff that I
我有一堆东西
don't care about it you know somewhere
不在乎你知道某个地方
buried in there is my create new file
埋在里面是我创建新文件
call but everything else is is just it's
电话，但其他一切就是
just making me miserable so you start
只是让我悲惨，所以你开始
thinking well that's unfortunate and and
好想这是不幸的，并且
then the next thing you think is well
那么你认为接下来的事情很好
maybe they didn't try hard enough on the
也许他们没有尽力
exception transparency from what if we
异常透明性，如果我们
use generics
使用泛型
so we say hey instead of using consumer
所以我们说嘿，而不是使用消费者
let's try an e consumer that can throw
让我们尝试一个可以抛出的电子消费者
some exception type e and while you
一些例外类型e
can't catch a generic exception type
无法捕获通用异常类型
you're certainly allowed to declare that
您当然可以声明
you throw it so this works out and then
你把它扔出去，这样就解决了，然后
we could even imagine hey if Java had
我们甚至可以想象嘿，如果Java有
done this in some sort of bizarro job
在某种奇怪的工作中做到了这一点
and then the iterable interface instead
然后是可迭代的接口
of having a for each method taking a
每个方法都有一个
consumer it could have taken an e
消费者本来可以
consumer and then everything would have
消费者，然后一切都会
just worked out the way that we want it
只是想出了我们想要的方式
to and and the funny thing is that this
到和有趣的是，这
actually works but it you'll you'll
确实有效，但是你会
notice right away the signature for each
立即通知每个人的签名
just got a little bit more confusing
只是有点混乱
because I suddenly have to put in this
因为我突然不得不把这个
extra generic parameter information but
额外的通用参数信息，但
you know on the whole I mean it does
你知道我的意思是
work it doesn't work if you have more
工作，如果你有更多的东西就行不通
than one type of exception that you need
而不是您需要的一种例外
to be able to declare that you throw you
才能宣布你丢了你
can try making your your thing generic
可以尝试使您的事情变得通用
and two parameters and type inference
和两个参数和类型推断
will just bail out on you completely and
会完全为您纾困，
so that that's not happy and and and and
所以那并不快乐
generally in the end you just decide
通常到最后你就决定了
it's it's probably not worth it and and
这可能不值得，并且
so you're sad and then you think you
所以你很难过，然后你以为你
know why am i sad I'm sad because of
知道为什么我难过我难过是因为
checked exceptions and now you think
检查异常，现在您认为
gosh checked exceptions and and how
天哪检查异常，以及如何
you're angry and and when we're angry we
你很生气，当我们生气时
sometimes do rash things and one of
有时会做些轻率的事情，其中​​之一
those rash things can be just to get rid
那些轻率的事情可能只是为了摆脱
of the problem and the solution is to
问题和解决方案是
just get rid of the problem so there are
只是摆脱问题，所以有
multiple libraries that can that do this
多个库可以做到这一点
I like the the Juke lambda library or
我喜欢Juke lambda库或
just the jewel library you can call it
只是珠宝库，你可以称之为
what they've done is for every
他们所做的每一件事
functional interface and the java.util
功能接口和java.util
function package they've created a
他们已经创建了一个功能包
companion interface with the name
随播介面名称
checked preceding it and that companion
在它和那个同伴之前检查
interface has the same method but it's
界面具有相同的方法，但是
allowed to throw any throwable and then
允许扔任何东西，然后
they've provided a series of static
他们提供了一系列静态
methods that will take in a for example
例如
a checked consumer and it will invoke
受检查的消费者，它将调用
the checks consumer and if any exception
检查消费者，如有异常
gets thrown it'll free throw that as a
被扔掉，它将作为一个罚球
run a runtime exception otherwise just
运行一个运行时异常否则
carries
携带
and so what this means is that now you
所以这意味着现在你
can write code like the following and
可以编写如下代码
all I have to do is say unchecked
我所要做的就是说不受限制
consumer and surround my lambda
消费者和我的lambda
expression with that and I'm back to -
这样表达，我回到-
you know where I can actually use things
你知道我可以实际使用的地方
now it's a little bit problematic
现在有点问题
because I I'm no longer actually
因为我不再是我了
throwing or declared to throw it an i/o
抛出或声明抛出I / O
exception I mean I could say that I do
例外，我的意思是我可以说我愿意
but I don't really anymore and so that's
但是我真的不再了，所以
that's a problem unless you want to
除非你想，否则这是一个问题
catch it and reconvert it so you know if
抓住并重新转换它，以便您知道是否
you think that there's a value in
你认为其中有价值
checked exceptions then that that's not
检查异常，那不是
so great and it's also a little more
太好了，还有一点
verbose so maybe not happy but at least
冗长，所以也许不快乐，但至少
you know we're no longer sad we're kind
你知道我们不再难过，我们很友善
of ok next thing I want to talk about is
接下来我想谈的是
design patterns so what's a design
设计模式是什么设计
pattern if you go to Wikipedia it says
模式，如果你去维基百科说
gosh it's a general repeatable solution
天哪，这是一个通用的可重复解决方案
to a commonly occurring problem Wow it's
常见问题哇
it's general it's it's a solution that
通常这是一种解决方案
sounds great and and it's for things
听起来很棒，而且很适合
that commonly happen what's what what's
通常发生什么是什么
not to like Stewart Holloway on the
不喜欢斯图尔特·霍洛威
other hand says it's a code smell they
另一只手说这是一种代码气味
tend to point to deficiencies in the
倾向于指出缺陷
language and the reason it's a smell is
语言及其气味的原因是
because of the third word and the
因为第三个字和
definition repeatable when you do a
定义在您执行时可重复
design pattern you are repeating some
您重复一些的设计模式
code that someone else has done and
别人做过的代码
you're repeating it over and over again
你要一遍又一遍地重复
a lot of the patterns are of the form
很多图案都是形式
here right this boilerplate code then do
在这里，这个样板代码然后
the thing you actually want to do and
你实际上想做的事情
then write some more boilerplate code
然后再写一些样板代码
and if you look at this with lambdas in
如果你用lambdas看看
mind you think ah I think we've got a
你介意啊，我想我们有一个
solution
解
so show a couple examples first pattern
所以先举几个例子
resource management sometimes called the
资源管理有时称为
dispose patterns so back in the days of
布置图案，以便追溯到
Java 6 or earlier whenever you want it
Java 6或更早版本
to deal with say an input stream you had
说一个输入流
to go through all this work you had to
完成所有这些工作
first get it and then you had to do a
首先得到它，然后你必须做一个
try block and then remember to close in
尝试阻止，然后记得关闭
the finally block not in the try block
最终块不在try块中
because you're not guaranteed you get to
因为你不能保证你会
the close statement otherwise you have
关闭声明，否则您将拥有
resource leaks and then everyone's
资源泄漏，然后每个人的
unhappy and so ok that that was bad and
不开心，还可以，那很糟糕，
in an attempt to both make this problem
试图都解决这个问题
less painful and also forestall the
减轻痛苦，也预防
introduction of
介绍
lambdas into the language josh bloch
lambdas融入语言josh bloch
said well why don't we why don't we have
说得好为什么我们不为什么我们没有
the new try with finally our issues to
最后尝试我们的问题的新尝试
try with resources syntax and so this
尝试使用资源语法，所以这
gets a lot better in Java 7 when I do
当我这样做时，Java 7会变得更好
this I don't need to worry about closing
这我不必担心关闭
the stream at all but there's a problem
流，但有一个问题
and that is well I don't know about you
那很好，我对你一无所知
but I'm getting old and forgetful and so
但是我变老了，健忘了，所以
I just might write something like this
我可能会写这样的东西
where I simply say hey let me just pass
我只是说嘿，让我过去
open stream into process and and and be
打开流并进入流程
done with it but now I'm not closing it
完成它，但现在我没有关闭它
and I've got a resource leak and it's a
而且我有资源泄漏，这是
poor API that lets people make mistakes
糟糕的API会让人们犯错误
so let's look I mean that that that's
所以让我们看一下我的意思是
not good and there there's actually
不好，实际上有
another problem too which is that this
另一个问题也是
whole language thing that was introduced
整个语言介绍
only works if you implement Auto
仅当您实现自动时才有效
closable so for example if I'd want to
可以关闭，例如，如果我想
use it for managing a lock I'm dealing
用它来管理我要处理的锁
with some bank account and I need to
有一些银行帐户，我需要
make sure that I'm exclusively accessing
确保我专门访问
it while I well I mess with it and I say
当我很好的时候我就搞砸了，我说
hey let's let's use try with resources
嘿，让我们尝试使用资源
for this and I am told that lock cannot
为此，我被告知锁不能
be converted to auto closeable which
转换为自动关闭
means that this language feature that
表示该语言功能
was introduced to help doesn't help me
被介绍来帮助我没有帮助
and so I'm sad but if you stop and think
所以我很伤心，但是如果你停下来思考
about this really even this was
关于这个，即使这是
problematic because not only could I
有问题的，因为我不仅可以
forget to close the lock I in some sense
忘记在某种意义上关闭锁
you shouldn't be able to get a hold of
你不应该掌握
an account and do something with it
一个帐户并对其进行处理
unless it's safe to access it and so
除非可以安全访问，否则
maybe instead of thinking about locks
也许不用考虑锁
all the time
每时每刻
let's let's have someone else manage
让我们让别人来管理
that for us and we get something like
对我们来说，我们得到类似
this we say ok here's an account manager
这是我们的客户经理
class and there's a lock inside and
上课，里面有一把锁
there's an account inside but note
里面有一个帐户，但请注意
they're private the public thing that we
他们是私人的，我们的公共事物
offer the API that we offer is the
提供我们提供的API是
ability to work with the account and
能够使用该帐户并
this API will handle getting the lock
该API将处理获取锁
and then doing the work that is
然后做的是
specified and then finally unlocking you
指定，然后最终为您解锁
can do exactly the same sort of thing
可以做完全一样的事情
with with the iostream example from
与iostream示例来自
earlier
较早
you've and this has actually been done I
你已经完成了
mean hibernates done this in the session
意思是冬眠在会议上这样做
API if you want to get the underlying
API，如果您想获取基础
sequel connection you do something
续集连接你做点什么
similar to this sort of trick and the
类似于这种技巧和
code now that I write actually looks
现在写的代码实际上看起来
really sweet because I just have to say
真的很甜蜜，因为我不得不说
what I want to do I want to work with
我想做的事
the account and what do I want to do I
帐户以及我想做什么
want to debit much more expressive much
想借记更多
less error-prone everything's nice we're
少出错的地方，一切都很好，我们
happy okay so you know we're so happy we
快乐好吧，所以你知道我们很高兴我们
think gosh maybe I'd like to take a
认为天哪，也许我想服用
break because I'm feeling lazy and and
休息，因为我感到懒惰，并且
laziness is another thing that there's a
懒惰是另一回事，
pattern for there's the the it's the
模式是有的
double check locking pattern that you've
仔细检查您的锁定模式
probably seen where you have to if you
可能看过你要去的地方
want to have a lazy evaluated if you
想要评估懒惰，如果您
want to evaluate something lazily you
想懒惰地评价你
you first get a lock or first you check
您首先获得锁或先检查
and see if it's already been evaluated
看看它是否已经被评估
if it hasn't you grab a lock and then
如果还没有，你就抓住一把锁，然后
you check again because memory models
您再次检查，因为内存型号
and then if you still don't have
然后如果你仍然没有
anything you go ahead and compute it and
进行任何计算并
you need to make sure to store it in a
您需要确保将其存储在
volatile variable or it doesn't actually
易失性变量或实际上不是
work so it's a lot of work to do so we
工作，所以要做很多工作
would like to be able to put that into a
希望能够将其放入
library and in fact this has been done
库，实际上这已经完成了
so another good library out there for
所以还有一个好的图书馆
dealing with lambda expressions is the
处理lambda表达式是
Babri library it used to be called java
Babri库，它以前被称为Java
slang but then Oracle said Java slang
Oracle语，但后来Oracle说Java lang语
that contains the word Java in it which
其中包含Java一词
is copyrighted so they turned the word
是受版权保护的，所以他们一字不漏
Java upside down and got Barbara it
Java颠倒了，让Barbara成功了
works when you look at their logo better
当您更好地看他们的徽标时，它可以工作
and it's got a good lazy implementation
而且有一个很好的懒惰实现
so we can we can just see how this works
这样我们就可以看到它是如何工作的
real quick so I can I can fire up Jay
真的很快，所以我可以解雇杰伊
shell if you haven't used Jay shell you
如果您没有用过杰伊，请给我壳
should be using Jay shell even if you're
应该使用Jay Shell，即使您
still on Java 8 have Java 9 sitting
仍在Java 8上安装Java 9
around so you can use JCL and then let's
周围，​​以便您可以使用JCL，然后让我们
see I'd better do some imports so import
看到我最好做一些进口，所以进口
everything I need and then I'll create a
我需要的一切，然后我将创建一个
lazy string here and and the works to
懒惰的字符串在这里和作品
compute this string is I'm going to
计算这个字符串是我要
print out some something to say that I'm
打印一些东西说我
thinking so we can see if the works
思考，所以我们可以看看是否有效
being done and then finally return some
完成后最后返回一些
value and since we're trying to be lazy
价值，因为我们正努力变得懒惰
it says write back to us we're a bum but
它说回信给我们，我们是流浪汉，但是
that's okay and I can actually say lazy
没关系，我实际上可以说懒
is this lazy method actually evaluated
这个懒惰的方法实际评估过吗
yet and I'll say no it's not
但我会说不，不是
but if I say lazy
但是如果我说懒
get it says I'm thinking and then it's
得到它说我在想，然后
it gives me back the answer and that's
它给了我答案，那就是
great and if I if asked it's been
很好，如果我问过
evaluated now it says of course it has
现在评估它说它当然有
been and if I say get a second time it
曾经，如果我说再来一次
doesn't have to compute it again so you
不必再次计算它，因此您
know another good example of a something
知道某事的另一个好例子
that was a pattern before and is now a
那是以前的模式，现在是
library method and when you think about
库方法以及何时考虑
all the code that had been written using
使用的所有代码
the double check locking pattern before
之前的双重检查锁定模式
people realize that it didn't work
人们意识到它没有用
unless it was volatile and then people
除非它不稳定，然后人们
had to go and change all that code if
必须去改变所有的代码，如果
the same thing had happened here it was
在这里发生了同样的事情
one library method that needed to be
一种需要的库方法
changed so big improvement lots of other
改变了这么大的进步
design patterns admits similar
设计模式承认相似
approaches but the the next thing that I
接近但我接下来的事情
want to talk about is ways that we can
想谈谈的是我们可以
increase type safety through lambdas
通过lambdas提高类型安全性
there are a lot of api's in Java which
Java中有很多api
rely on the these API is typically are
依赖这些API通常是
ones that are using reflection in some
在某些情况下使用反射的
way and they may rely on the use of
方式，他们可能会依靠使用
strings to tell them what to reflect for
告诉他们要反映什么的字符串
this is a not strongly typed code it's a
这不是一个强类型的代码，它是一个
string ly typed I don't remember who
字符串输入，我不记得是谁
first said that but it's a perfect way
首先说，但这是一个完美的方法
of phrasing it and it's it's a problem
措辞，这是一个问题
because refactoring tools don't really
因为重构工具并不是真的
know that you're talking about a method
知道你在说一种方法
name if you've got it in quotes and the
名称，如果您用引号引起来，
compiler doesn't know so it's not going
编译器不知道，所以不会
to be able to catch typos at compile
能够在编译时捕捉错别字
time which means you're deferring things
时间，这意味着你推迟了事情
to runtime which typically might happen
到运行时，通常可能会发生
you know during a demo to your boss or
您在向老板演示时知道
something like that or in you know
那样的东西或你知道的东西
actual live production which not so good
实际的现场制作不是很好
but lambda expressions offer a great
但是lambda表达式提供了很好的
alternative here and in fact the first
在这里，实际上是第一个
example of this let's let's take a look
这个例子让我们看一下
at what it takes to make a comparator so
做一个比较器需要什么
if you remember the contract for
如果您还记得合同
comparator it's a little bit complicated
比较器有点复杂
because you need to make sure that
因为你需要确保
there's sort of this anti symmetry and
这种反对称性
there's this consistency and there's a
有这种一致性，有一个
bunch of things and so it's easy to
一堆东​​西，所以很容易
write a comparator and get it wrong so
写一个比较器，弄错了，所以
it's good to have some sort of library
拥有某种图书馆是很好的
that lets you do it that'll do it for
让您做到这一点
you excuse me and so the the common
你原谅我，所以普通人
beans utils package from Apache Commons
Apache Commons的beans utils软件包
has an API that allows you to do
有一个API，可让您执行
and you have to build a comparator chain
你必须建立一个比较器链
and then you can say well first let's
然后你可以说很好，让我们
say I'm comparing people let me compare
说我在比较人让我比较
on last name and if if I get a tie let
在姓氏上，如果我得到领带，
me do a tiebreaker based on the first
我会根据第一个
name and unfortunately this was done
名称，不幸的是这样做
without great attention to generics
无需过多关注泛型
probably was done before generics so I
大概是在仿制药之前完成的，所以我
actually have to cast it to get what I
实际上必须投下它才能得到我
want so this doesn't look so good but a
想要这样看起来不太好但是
lot of that is not the fault of Java
很多不是Java的错
that was just the API we could have had
那只是我们本来可以拥有的API
a better looking API that said ok here I
一个看起来更好的API，在这里我可以说
just want a comparator chain on the
只想要比较器链
person class and I want to you know use
人类，我想你知道用
last name and tiebreak on first name so
姓和名的抢七游戏
this is definitely an improvement but
这绝对是一个进步，但是
it's still string ly typed there's still
它仍然是字符串输入，仍然
opportunities for problems and problems
问题的机会和问题
make us sad it turns out this one is
让我们伤心的是，这是
actually solved in the jdk itself the
实际上在jdk本身解决了
comparator class added a few new methods
比较器类添加了一些新方法
the most interesting one is the
最有趣的是
comparing or the most interesting pair I
比较或最有趣的一对
guess is the first is comparing the
猜测是第一个是比较
static method that says I want to create
我要创建的静态方法
a comparator which compares based off of
比较器，基于
some function which Maps my being or my
一些映射我的存在或我的存在的函数
whatever to something that is already
对已经存在的东西
implementing comparable and then the
实施可比性，然后
other great method is the then comparing
另一个很棒的方法是
method that says and if that doesn't if
说的方法，如果不是
that can't you know distinguish the two
那你不知道区分两者
things then let's try and let's try this
然后让我们尝试，让我们尝试一下
other method so you can create now a
其他方法，因此您现在可以创建一个
comparator in just a couple of lines of
比较器仅需几行
code and that couple of lines of code is
代码，这几行代码是
completely typesafe your ID he's going
完全保护您要输入的ID
to know about it your refactoring tools
了解它的重构工具
are going to know about it code analysis
将要了解它的代码分析
tools assuming that they're there
假设他们在那里的工具
they're up to speed on lambdas are all
他们要加快lambda的速度
going to be able to handle this
将能够处理这个
perfectly well and and so again you know
很好，所以你又知道
that that's great it's taking out a look
那很棒，它看起来像
at another example so this one is I'm
在另一个例子中，这个是我
gonna be talking about J unit 5 because
将会谈论J单元5，因为
it just recently came out and it looks
它刚出来，看起来
kind of Boston actually and and they
实际上是波士顿，而他们
have a way of a few ways of doing
有几种方法
parameterised tests one way is to just
参数化测试的一种方法是
have an annotation above your test with
在您的测试上方有一个注释
a series of strings and each string is
一系列的字符串，每个字符串是
supposed to somehow represent the
应该以某种方式代表
various data that you want
您想要的各种数据
providing to your test I should mention
提供给您的测试我应该提到
a parameterised test is basically a test
参数化测试基本上就是测试
that runs with different values and you
以不同的值运行，而您
sort of provide the values one by one so
一点一点地提供值
it's a way of writing a lot of tests
这是编写大量测试的一种方式
without writing a lot of code so that's
无需编写大量代码，因此
nice the the the annotation approach
注释方法很好
where you list all the parameters in the
您在其中列出了所有参数
annotation is not that flexible it only
注释不是那么灵活
works if you've got one parameter so
如果您有一个参数，则可以正常工作
more generally they have this thing
更普遍地说，他们有这个东西
where you can say you've got some method
你可以说你有一些方法
that returns say a stream of arguments
返回说一堆参数
where arguments are basically some sort
其中参数基本上是某种形式
of tuple and then you can write your
元组，然后你可以写你的
parameterize test that looks like this
参数化看起来像这样的测试
you say I it's a parameterised test
你说我是参数测试
instead of a regular test and the data
而不是常规测试和数据
is gonna come from this method string
将来自此方法字符串
int values and then I've got my test
整数值，然后我进行了测试
that I actually run I want to verify
我确实要确认
that if I if I parse the or excuse me if
如果我解析了或者对不起
I take a the integer and and turn it
我取一个整数，然后将其旋转
into a string that I get what I'm
变成我所得到的字符串
expecting to get so so that's that's
期望得到这样，那就是
good that this is very good but it is
很好，这很好，但是
string ly typed and and so there's a few
字符串类型，所以有一些
problems the first is I might misspell
问题首先是我可能拼错了
string it values obviously but there's
字符串值很明显，但是有
another deeper problem here which is
另一个更深层次的问题是
that while my test int value of method
那当我测试方法的int值时
takes a string and an int I have no
需要一个字符串和一个我没有的整数
guarantees that that's actually what's
保证那实际上是什么
returned from the string and values
从字符串和值返回
method it's just a stream of arguments
方法，它只是一个参数流
and those argument instances might not
这些参数实例可能不会
have a string and an int they might not
有一个字符串和一个整数，他们可能没有
even have just two elements might have
甚至只有两个元素
one or three so leaves a little bit to
一或三片叶子
be desired but it turns out there's
被期望，但事实证明
another thing in J unit five which is
第五单元的另一件事是
really awesome that allows us to fix
真棒，可以修复
this and what it's called is the dynamic
这就是所谓的动态
test so dynamic test in J unit is
测试，所以以J为单位的动态测试是
basically a way of creating tests at
基本上是在
runtime instead of completely specifying
运行时而不是完全指定
them at compile time and the funny thing
他们在编译时和有趣的事情
is that in this particular case we can
在这种特殊情况下，我们可以
defer things to runtime in a way that
将事情推迟到运行时
gives us more compile time type safety
给我们更多的编译时类型安全性
which is an irony I just love and and
我只是喜欢而具有讽刺意味的是，
the way we can do it is well for the
我们可以做到的方式对
example we had before first of all on
首先我们之前的例子
and I'm gonna use the the tuple class
我将使用元组类
from again jook lambda
再次从乔克·拉姆达
lots of different libraries provide
许多不同的库提供
tuples these days but it's a nice type
这些天的元组，但这是一个不错的类型
safe class it's parameterised in the
安全类，它在
generically parameterised in the type of
一般以以下类型进行参数化
the first and second element of your
您的第一个和第二个元素
tuple and so I've got a stream of tuples
元组，所以我有一个元组流
of string and int and then what I want
字符串和整数，然后是我想要的
to do is I want to take each one of
我要做的是把
those and the the first map is a map
那些，第一张地图是一张地图
from the stream class the second map
从流类第二张地图
that you see here is a map from the
您在这里看到的是来自
tuple class which is a little bit weird
元组类有点奇怪
and try not to worry about it too much
并尽量不要担心太多
right now but the upshot is once I'm
现在，但是结果是我
down to something that takes a string
下降到需要弦的东西
and an integer then build my dynamic
然后一个整数建立我的动态
test and when I build my dynamic test I
测试，当我建立动态测试时
need to first say what is that the test
首先要说的是测试
should be called so that when it passes
应该被调用，以便它通过时
or fails it shows up nicely on the
或失败，它很好地显示在
output and then secondly the actual test
输出，然后进行实际测试
and this works and it's great it's
这很有效，很好
typesafe but it's a little bit messy
类型安全，但有点混乱
because there's this weird map tuple map
因为有这个奇怪的地图元组地图
thing that's going on that I don't want
我不想发生的事情
to have to think about and I don't know
要考虑，我不知道
I it doesn't feel as clean as it could
我感觉不太干净
be to me but if we create one small
对我来说，但如果我们创造一个小
static helper method we can make things
静态助手方法，我们可以做的事情
a lot better so here's a method
好多了，这是一种方法
parameter and this this one takes in
参数，这是一个
functions with two arguments and then
有两个参数的函数，然后
you could create a similar version for
您可以为创建一个类似的版本
three and four and five and so forth
三，四，五等等
arguments but the way it works is you
论据，但它的运作方式是你
you say well I take in a test that I
你说好我参加了一个考试
want to sort or a test creator that I
想排序还是我的测试创建者
want to run and and I take in some data
想跑步，我拿了一些数据
and I do that funky double map thing
而且我做那个时髦的双重地图
that I did before and the idea is you
我以前做过的，想法是你
write this once get it to compile and
编写一次，将其编译并
then never worry about it again and
然后再也不用担心了
instead write tests using it so now if I
而是使用它编写测试，所以现在如果我
want to write a parametrized test i say
我想写一个参数化测试
i've got my test method and it's it's a
我有我的测试方法，这是一个
test Factory and I'm gonna use the
测试工厂，我将使用
parametrized method to let everything
参数化的方法让一切
work out nicely and I'm just going to
锻炼得很好，我只是要
start off by saying what's the test it's
首先说一下测试是什么
a dynamic test based off s and I I'm not
基于s的动态测试，但我不是
even bothering to specify the types here
甚至在这里指定类型
compiler inference is doing all of that
编译器推断正在完成所有这些工作
for me and doing it correctly and so as
为我做正确的事情
before the first thing I do is give my
在我要做的第一件事之前，先给我
to name and then I say what I actually
命名，然后我说我实际上
want to do in the test and then finally
想在测试中做，然后最后
the last thing I do is I provide some
我要做的最后一件事是我提供一些
test data now I don't know about you but
现在测试数据我不了解你，但是
this makes me this is the way you want
这让我这就是你想要的方式
to write tests if you're writing
如果您正在编写测试，就可以编写测试
parameterize tests because now you're
参数化测试，因为现在您
just saying what you want to do and you
只是说你想做什么而你
don't have any of the string ly typed
没有任何类型的字符串
mess that was going on before and in
之前和之中发生的混乱
fact I like this stuff so much that I
事实上我非常喜欢这个东西
wanted it even before J unit five had
甚至在第五单元J想要之前
really been built and so I ended up
真的被建造，所以我最终
writing a quick library for J unit four
为J单元4编写一个快速库
it's a it's a test runner called Lam
这是一个名为Lam的测试跑步者
data Runner I don't have the URL but if
data Runner我没有网址，但是如果
you google it it's going to be the only
你谷歌它将是唯一的
thing that shows up under that and it
在它下面出现的东西
basically has an API that lets you do
基本上有一个API，可以让您
pretty much the same thing it does
几乎一样的事情
require the use of a special test Runner
需要使用特殊的测试运行器
which can cause problems and because of
这可能会导致问题，并且由于
the way it works
工作方式
certain J unit rules don't work out so
某些J单位规则行不通，所以
nicely so it's not perfect but it's it's
很好，所以它不是完美的，但是它是
a nice way and I've actually found it
一个很好的方法，我实际上已经找到了
quite useful and again not a lot of code
很有用，再次没有很多代码
to take something that is painful and
服用一些痛苦的东西
turn it into something that's really
把它变成真正的东西
nice and and better type safety okay
更好的类型安全性还可以
last thing I want to talk about is a few
我想谈的最后一件事是
best practices for for API design the
API设计的最佳做法
first is and this goes back to the file
首先是，这回到文件
visitor example if you're creating new
如果您要创建新的访客示例
interfaces if possible create them so
接口（如果可能）创建它们
that they only have one method it might
他们只有一种方法
actually be better to have four
其实有四个更好
interfaces each taking in a single
接口各取一个
method than one large interface if you
比一个大接口的方法，如果您
can get away with that and barring that
可以逃脱并禁止
consider providing people factory
考虑提供人工厂
methods to create instances of your
创建您的实例的方法
interface so that they can use lambdas
界面，以便他们可以使用lambdas
and enjoy them next rule don't create
并享受他们的下一条规则
any interfaces at all instead use the
根本不使用任何接口
ones that are already out there Java
那些已经存在的Java
util function has a number of great
util函数有很多很棒的功能
interfaces in it and because they're all
接口，因为它们都是
type current generically parameterised
类型当前通用参数化
they're gonna work for probably 80% of
他们可能会为80％
your use cases and then another 10% of
您的用例，然后再用10％
your use cases they would work except
您的用例，除了
that you have checked exceptions you
您已经检查了例外情况
need to worry about
需要担心
and so then you can use say the Juke
所以你可以用说Juke
lamda library again to manage those
lamda图书馆再次管理那些
checked exceptions this is nice you know
检查异常，这很好，您知道
less classes to load in less things for
更少的类可以在更少的东西中加载
people to think about they'll say Oh a
人们想一想他们会说哦
function yes I know what that is I don't
功能是的，我知道那是什么我不知道
need to go back to the drawing board and
需要回到绘图板，
try to figure out what this new
尝试找出这个新东西
interface that you gave me is I already
你给我的界面已经是我了
understand exactly what it is another
确切了解这是什么
thing so sometimes you want you you have
东西，所以有时候你想要你拥有
a method and let's say I've got an API
一种方法，假设我有一个API
that has a method in it to do some work
里面有做一些工作的方法
and it takes in a runnable and then I
它需要一个可运行的，然后我
think you know checked exceptions that's
以为您知道检查的异常
gonna make people sad so let me also
会让人伤心，所以也让我
accept a checked runnable one that won't
接受一个不会被检查的可运行的
throw any checked exceptions it's a
抛出任何检查的异常
weird naming convention in my opinion
我认为奇怪的命名约定
but whatever and this seems like a nice
但是无论如何，这似乎是一个不错的选择
thing to do but the problem is that both
要做的事情，但问题是两者
these lambdas from the compilers point
从编译器角度来看这些lambda
of view have the same shape they both
两者的形状相同
take in no arguments and return no
不接受参数，不返回
arguments and throws clauses aren't
不是参数和throws子句
considered which means that if I want to
考虑到这意味着如果我想
pass anything into this as a lambda the
将任何东西作为lambda传递给
compiler is gonna say it's ambiguous and
编译器会说它是模棱两可的
it's gonna force me to instead cast my
这将迫使我反而抛弃我的
lambda expression as either a runnable
lambda表达式可运行
or a checked runnable which just feels
或感觉到的已检查可运行
ridiculous so we knew overload methods
荒谬的，所以我们知道重载方法
make sure you don't overload methods in
确保您不重载方法
a way that you might force your callers
一种可能迫使您的来电者
to actually specify which kind of lambda
实际指定哪种lambda
flavor they're passing in um if the land
土地传来的味道
does have different shapes it works out
确实有不同的形状
fine so for example if if one of these
很好，例如，如果其中之一
was a runnable and one of these was a
是可运行的，其中之一是
callable well those have different
可召唤的那些有不同的
shapes because callable actually returns
形状，因为可调用实际上返回
something as whereas runnable doesn't or
某种东西，而可运行的不是
let you know different parameters and so
让您知道不同的参数等等
forth but try to avoid that the last
来回但尽量避免最后
best practice that i can recommend is to
我可以推荐的最佳做法是
fill out the session survey always
始终填写会话调查
really appreciate feedback I mean
非常感谢我的反馈
obviously if if you if you liked this
显然如果你喜欢的话
talk then I'm glad to hear about that
聊聊，然后我很高兴得知
but I also want to hear about it if you
但我也想听听
didn't like it what I could have done
不喜欢我本可以做的
better and I even want to hear about it
更好，我什至想听听
if you're really angry so with that we
如果你真的很生气，那么我们
have a few minutes if there are any
有几分钟的时间
questions yes the question was do I ever
问题是，问题是我曾经吗
think Java will move all the checked
认为Java将移动所有已检查的
exceptions to runtime exceptions
运行时异常
theoretically they could because in some
理论上他们可以，因为在某些情况下
sense it wouldn't break any existing
感觉不会破坏任何现有的
code but from what I've heard people
代码，但据我所知
like Marc Ron mark Reinhold and Brian
像马克·罗恩·马克·莱因霍尔德和布莱恩
gets and now it's buck we say in various
得到，现在它是降压，我们在各种
forums it's probably gonna be a cold day
论坛可能会很冷
down below before that happens so you
在发生这种情况之前下降到下面
know fortunately increasingly when
幸运的是，越来越知道
people create new exception types they
人们创建新的异常类型
extend runtime exceptions so you know
扩展运行时异常，以便您知道
it's not getting a lot worse yes
并没有恶化很多，是的
question okay so the question what if
问题好吧，如果
I'm processing a stream of data and
我正在处理数据流，
there's one piece of data in the stream
流中只有一条数据
which is kind of a poison pill it's
这是一种毒药
gonna cause a runtime exception and now
会导致运行时异常，现在
my entire stream processing is upended
我的整个流处理都颠倒了
and and and thrown out and how do I deal
然后扔出去，我该如何处理
with that well it's a little bit tricky
这么好有点棘手
I mean obviously one thing you can do is
我的意思是显然你可以做的一件事是
is swallow the exception but that
吞下例外，但那
doesn't feel quite right so maybe what
感觉不对，所以也许
you want to do then is if it's a map
你想做的就是如果它是一张地图
operation for example instead of mapping
例如操作而不是映射
to the result you're interested in you
对您感兴趣的结果
could map to something that is either
可以映射到
the result or an exception so you can
结果或异常，以便您可以
kind of accumulate all those exceptions
积累所有这些例外
at the end I think I think bobber might
最后我想我觉得浮子可能
have an either type that you can use for
有一种您可以用于的类型
that sort of thing so yeah if that's
这样的事情，是的，如果那是
something you're worried about it that
你担心的事情
that's what I would recommend is is have
我建议的是
some way of collecting the exceptions go
一些收集异常的方法
from there
从那里
other questions all right well I
其他问题都很好我
apologize this talk was so fast I was
抱歉，我的谈话太快了
worried about not being able to finish
担心无法完成
in time and ended up actually finishing
及时地完成了
a couple minutes early but that means
提前几分钟，但这意味着
that you all can get into the the wait
你们所有人都可以进入等待
list line for your next favorite talk
下一个您喜欢的演讲的清单行
and thank you
谢谢你
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]